Your browser does not support JavaScript!             

SEO POWERSUITE PRIVACY POLICY
=============================

Effective Date: May 11, 2021  
  
When you use SEO PowerSuite or any of the products included therein (all together and each individually called "**SEO PowerSuite**") or our website [https://www.link-assistant.com/](https://www.link-assistant.com/) and https://www.seopowersuite.com (and other available domains such as .fr, .de, .nl, .jp, .es, .ru.) ("**Website**") we can collect some of your **Personal Data** (which means information about you, which can directly or indirectly identify you).  
  
We take the privacy and security of your Personal Data very seriously. We do not sell your Personal Data and do not earn money from your Personal Data in any other way. Our goal is to provide you with SEO tools while respecting your privacy and obligations. Our business model is simple: we only make money if you choose to pay for our tools by purchasing a license. This means that great products and services are our main assets and keeping your data private is one of our operating principles.  
  
We take numerous measures to protect your Personal Data from accidental loss or theft.  
  
This Privacy Policy describes:  
· How we process your Personal Data, including using cookies,  
· With whom we can share your Personal Data, and  
· The choices you have regarding your Personal Data.  
  
**Data controller:**  
Techfusion LTD  
A.G. Leventi, 5, THE LEVENTIS GALLERY TOWER, 13th floor, Flat/Office 1301, 1097, Nicosia, Cyprus  
  
We may periodically update this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of SEO PowerSuite after the effective date of the updated Privacy Policy will be subject to the new Privacy Policy. If we make any major changes to our Privacy Policy and will need your explicit consent for further processing of your Personal Data, we will request your consent or your renewed consent (in case it was obtained previously).  
  
**If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, PLEASE do not download, install or use SEO PowerSuite, and you shall PERMANENTLY DESTROY ALL COPIES OF SEO POWERSUITE**.  

HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA
--------------------------------

| **Type of Personal Data we collect** | **How do we use it** | **Legal ground for the processing** |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Upon registration via the Website, you provide us with your **name** and **e-mail address** | To identify you in our system and to provide you the correct access to SEO PowerSuite and relevant services | Agreement with you (Terms of Use) or your request before entering into such an agreement |
| We can also use your e-mail address to send you service-related communications until you opt out of receiving such communications | Our mutual legitimate interest based on the balance of interests, which is that you get the best services and offers from us |
| If you request technical support via the Website, you also provide us with your **name, e-mail address**, and the **text of your request** | We use this information to respond to your request | Our mutual legitimate interest based on the balance of interests to ensure safe usage of SEO PowerSuite |
| When you use the Website, we may also automatically collect some of your **technical data**, such as information about your device, and information about your use of the Website (**usage data**) by using cookie technology. | We may use such data as follows:<br><br>* **to keep the Website safe and fair** (analyze and monitor the use of the Website, take action against fraudulent or misbehaving users, etc.),<br>* **to offer you our great services**, including through the use of third-party cookies (more about cookies below) | Our mutual legitimate interest based on the balance of interests to provide you better services based |

We do not process your payment information. Your payment information is processed by our third-parties payments providers.  

COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES
--------------------------------

Cookies are small text files sent to your computer, which enables services and website features to function properly.  
  
We have created and implemented our cookies and cookies from third parties for analytical and marketing purposes. Analytical and marketing cookies, among other things, collect information on how users use the Website and the effectiveness of our third-party advertising.  
  
Below is the list of our third-party cookies and the purpose for which we engaged each third party:

| **Name of such third party** | **Its privacy policy** | **How such third party uses your Personal Data** |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Google Analytics | https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites | To analyze your user experience and, based on the results, improve our service to you |
| Facebook Analytics | [https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy) |
| Yandex Mertica | https://metrica.yandex.com/about/info/privacy-policy |
| Bing Universal Event Tracking | [https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-US/privacystatement](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-US/privacystatement) |     |
| Facebook ads | https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy | To provide you advertising that will fit your interests |
| Twitter | https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/twitter-cookies | To provide you advertising that will fit your interests |

You can generally activate or later deactivate the use of cookies through a functionality built into your browser.  

THIRD PARTIES WHO MAY HAVE ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL DATA
-------------------------------------------------------

We may share your Personal Data only if it is strictly necessary to provide you services and only to our cookie providers (as listed above) and the following service providers:

| **Name of such third party** | **Its privacy policy** | **How such third party uses your Personal Data** |
| --- | --- | --- |
| 2сheckout | https://www.2checkout.com | To process your payments |
| Paypal | https://www.paypal.com |
| Universal Event Tracking | https://microsoft.com | User Analytics |
| Sleeknote | https://sleeknote.com | Marketing automation |
| Mailchimp | https://mailchimp.com | Marketing automation |
| GetResponse | https://www.getresponse.com | Marketing automation |

YOUR RIGHTS AND OPTIONS
-----------------------

You have the right to access the Personal Data we hold about you, correct your Personal Data, have your Personal Data deleted, object to how we process or share your Personal Data, restrict how we process or share your Personal Data, withdraw your consent.  
  
We process and answer your requests without undue delay and in any event within one month of our receipt of the request unless a longer period is required due to the complexity of the request. In this case, our response time can be up to three months in total.  
  
**Rights of California residents**  
  
Under California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) you have a right to request business stops selling Personal Data to third parties (but note that we are not selling your Personal Data), to be informed about what categories of Personal Data we are collecting, request us to delete the Personal Data we have collected in the past 12 months. We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your rights granted under CCPA.  
  
As required by CCPA we endeavor to respond to a verifiable request within 45 days of its receipt. If we require more time (up to 90 days), we will inform you of the reason and extension period in writing. We will deliver our written response by e-mail.  
  
Please note that we may require you to verify your identity before processing your request.  
  
**Data deletion**. Note that if you ask us to delete your Personal Data, we can retain your Personal Data as necessary to comply with our legal obligations or resolve disputes (for instance, while you have outstanding debts to us). After deleting your Personal Data, which includes your e-mail address and name, you won't be able to continue using SEO PowerSuite.  
  
If you don't want your Personal Data to be deleted, but you no longer want to receive the emails, you can opt out of receiving the emails by pressing the "Unsubscribe" button in any email or by contacting us with the relevant request. After this, you will no longer receive the emails, but your data will not be deleted. Please note that if you opt out of receiving the emails you may miss out on great deals or discounts.
